GITHUB LINKEDIN PORTFOLIO E-MAIL 343-202-0214

PROFILE

Talented and experienced front-end developer with 2+ years of experience executing with plenty of diverse skills. Experience has taught me to take accessibility and responsiveness seriously, and I am delighted to continue my career with a focus on the web readily accessible, entirely responsive, and intuitive for users.

EDUCATION

- Algonquin College, Ottawa Interactive Media Design, 2021 - April 23
- 2. Maharaja Sayajirao University, India Communications, 2016 2019

SKILLS

- TAILWIND CSS
- JavaScript / TypeScript
- React
- Github
- HubSpot
- Shopify
- Wordpress
- PHP / Laravel

CERTIFICATIONS

- Microsoft Advertising Certified Professional
- <u>Microsoft Advertising Native & Display</u>
 <u>Certification</u>
- Microsoft Advertising Shopping Certification
- Microsoft Advertising Search Certification
- SEO Certified HubSpot Academy
- Social Media Certified HubSpot Academy
- Digital Marketing HubSpot Academy
- Design Thinking and Innovation by Harvard Business School Online

EXPERIENCE

SALES ASSOCIATE, CANADIAN TIRE, CARLING AVENUE – 2021 – 2022

Identifying low stock levels and maintain inventory accuracy. Ensuring that retail basics tasks are executed efficiently. Answering questions and providing friendly advice and services to customers. Responding to and handling customer inquiries, requests and concerns in a timely manner, over the phone and in person. Locating products in the warehouse. Meeting and greeting customers and providing friendly, informed service to them. Guiding customer to the location of requested items.

SALES ASSOCIATE, BOMBAY SPICES, WEST HUNT CLUB ROAD – 2021 – 2021

Followed department protocols for product preparation, storage, rotation, and stocking. Product quality and freshness are monitored, and adequate product rotation is ensured. Helped with inventory inspections on a regular basis. Arrives on time, well groomed, clothed, and prepared to work; performs all planned shifts and attends mandatory trainings and meetings. Provided exceptional customer service, handled client requirements in a fast and effective manner, and modelled suggestive selling strategies; promptly and courteously answered phones and emails. Maintained a clean and hygienic working and shopping environment; by keeping equipment clean and safe in compliance with WFM cleanliness and safety requirements.

CASHIER, CIRCLE K, WALKLEY ROAD -2020 - 2021

Stocked shelves, kept the store clean, and took away the trash at the end of the shift. Pulled out expired items and storing them in a separate room, as well as reconciling lottery and paperwork at the conclusion of each shift.

GITHUB LINKEDIN PORTFOLIO E-MAIL 343-202-0214